Keri Rogosz

Licensed Esthetician

9834 Presidential Dr Allison Park, PA 15090 (878) 302-2165 Krogosz17@gmail.com

SKILLS

Experience with salon grade products. Skill with multiple machines such as Galvanic and high frequency machines. Proficiency with Brow and Lash tinting, Knowledge with Hard, Soft, Honey, and Paraffin Wax and sugaring. Ability to operate Microdermabrasion. Background with Chemical Peels such as PCA. Thorough understanding of Infection Control. Experience with Ingredients and Chemistry. Vast knowledge of Anatomy and Physiology. Certified Makeup Artist. Proficient use of Woodslamp. Lastly, ability to preform Body Wraps on clients.

EDUCATION

North Hills Beauty Academy, Location — Licensed Esthetician

Graduated November 2021

Deer Lakes High School, Location — *HighSchool Diploma*

Graduated 2018

Extracurricular Activities

Hampton and West Deer Police Academy Training: Trained in many life saving tactics such as CPR, how to handle emergency situations, and understand the many situations that our local officers have to handle on a daily basis

Girl Scouts:Learned many skills that followed for life such as teamwork, hard work, perseverance, and ambition.

ChildCare and Dog sitting: Cared for, and raised several family members, and local dogs.

EXPERIENCE

Walmart, Pittsburgh Mills — General Employee

January 2017 - 2018

Fast paced work environment. Time management, with much freedom to make your workload fit into your hours.

Wildwood, Wildwood Road — Opening Supervisor

February 2018 - December 2019

Opening of the facility with minimal supervision. Customer care, and problem solving.

Target, Mcknight Road — Stocking Associate

March 2021 - Current
Essential employe
during the pandemic.
Experience with
handling constant
sanitisation and a
clean environment.